{"data":[{"question":"You ______ (be) in Rome tonight.","a":"shall be","b":"will be","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the future simple tense to talk about future (tonight)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"You ______ (have) time to help me tomorrow?","a":"Will you have","b":"Shall you have","c":"a & b","answer":"1","explain":"- Future simple: used to ask somebody to do something politely\n- Will + S + V...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"Do you think that he ______ (recognize) me?","a":"shall recognize","b":"will recognize","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- You\/they\/it\/he\/she + will + infinitive.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"I hope I ______ (find) it.","a":"shall find","b":"will find","c":"a & b","answer":"3","explain":"- I\/we + will\/shall + infinitive.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"If petrol pump attendants go on strike we ______ (not have) any petrol.","a":"shall not have","b":"won't have","c":"a & b","answer":"3","explain":"- Use conditional sentence type I form","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"Newspaper announcement: The President ______ (drive) along the High Street in an open carriage.","a":"shall drive","b":"will drive","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use future simple tense to anounce somethig that happen in the future","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"You ______ (need) a visa if you are going to Spain.","a":"shall need","b":"will need","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use conditional sentence type I form","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"If you open that trapdoor you ______ (see) some steps.","a":"shall see","b":"will see","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use conditional sentence type I form","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"She ______ (have) 1000 a year when she is twenty-one.","a":"shall have","b":"will have","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use future simple tense to talk about the future","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"I wonder if he ______ (succeed).","a":"shall succeed","b":"will succeed","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the future simple tense when you wonder about something","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"I wonder if he ______ (succeed).","a":"shall succeed","b":"will succeed","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the future simple tense when you wonder about something","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"}]}